http://www.apu.edu/about/site/privacy/

About This Site
Web Accessibility
Privacy PolicyUnsubscribeFull Privacy PolicyGlossary of TermsContact Information
Privacy Policy
Azusa Pacific University respects your privacy rights and has adopted clear guidelines for all of its departments and offices requiring that information you submit is only to be used for the purposes for which you have consented. Azusa Pacific University will never sell or rent any personal information collected from you to any third party. The following summarizes key points in our full privacy policy.
General Data Protection Regulation
Current students, student applicants, employees, potential employees, or other individuals located in a European Union country, Iceland, Liechtenstein, Norway, or Switzerland who provide APU with personal data are now afforded new widespread privacy rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) effective May 25, 2018. Read the full GDPR Policy.
Data Collection
We do collect personal information.
We do use cookies.
We do track online activity.
We do not allow third-party tracking.
Learn more about our data collection policies.
Data Use and Sharing
We do not use your personal information without your consent.
We do not sell or rent your personal information.
We do use reasonable means to keep information secure.
Learn more about our data use and sharing policies.
Privacy Rights
You can opt out or control how the information you submit online is used/shared
You can alter/update your information
We have a dispute resolution process.
Learn more about our privacy rights policies.
Scope
This Privacy Policy covers information provided to Azusa Pacific University online at the following websites:
Main APU Website
Bookstore Website
Graduate Online Application
Alumni Website
This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected through means other than the APU websites listed above, and does not cover the following internal Azusa Pacific University websites:
APU Intranet
APU Canvas
For more information, read the Office of Career Services’ Privacy Policy (PDF).
Pages in this SectionPrivacy PolicyUnsubscribeFull Privacy PolicyGlossary of TermsContact InformationFull Menu
